Guide to the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection, 1579-1961
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection
1579-1961
C0213
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
5 linear feet (90 folders)
Donated to George Mason University Libraries in September 1978 by the Mann family, the C. Harrison Mann Jr, Map Collection comprises ninety-six maps ranging from the sixteenth to nineteenth centuries and is housed in the Special Collections & Archives department. Though the majority of the maps Mann collected are of Virginia, there are many pertaining to other parts of the United States and the world in the collection.
Mann, Charles Harrison, Jr., 1908-1977
Biographical note
Charles Harrison Mann, Jr. was born in Alabama in 1908 and received his law degree from the University of Virginia in 1931. He subsequently became an attorney both in Washington, D.C. and in Arlington, Virginia where he and his wife Betty Hart Mann, maintained their home. In 1949, while serving as President of the Northern Virginia Chapter of the University of Virginia Alumni Association, Mann organized an exploratory committee of local citizens to develop support for higher education in Northern Virginia. Through these efforts, the Northern Virginia Center of the University opened in October 1, 1949.
In 1953 Mann organized the Advisory Council to the Northern Virginia Center, which agreed that a two-year branch college should be established. Elected as a Democrat to the Virginia House of Delegates from 1954-1970, Mann sponsored a resolution calling for a study of educational needs for Virginia, and was instrumental in recommending the development of a college system in Virginia, particularly the establishment of a branch in Northern Virginia.
Mann was responsible for creating an educational financial assistance program for Virginia college students, and was instrumental in sponsoring legislation allowing local governments to form regional boards to acquire and transfer land and buildings for educational use.
He also served as the Chairman of George Mason College's first Board of Control. He sponsored bills constituting George Mason College as a branch of the University of Virginia and later elevating it to a four year division of the University with the right to grant degrees and offer graduate programs. He served on the GMU Board of Visitors from 1975 to 1977. He died in 1977.
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds and handwritten draft of his history of George Mason University. Papers pertain to his political career and include subject files, memoranda, campaign materials, speeches, newsclippings and other related materials. In addition, there is the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. collection of rare books and atlases that can be found searching the GMU Libraries catalog.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by size of map.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Betty Hart Mann in 1979.
Alternative Form Available
Selections from the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection are also available in the.
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
America--Discovery and exploration-Maps.; Virginia--Maps.
Document Types:
Maps.
Contents List
- C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection
  - Nova Virginiae Tabula, circa 1660 (Folder 1)
    New Virginia Map published ca. 1660 by Joan Blaeu (1597-1663) of Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 20.125 in. x 24.25 in. (51.12 cm x 62.23 cm). Map depicting seventeenth-century Virginia. Titlepiece in upper center. Vignettes of Chief Powhatan in upper left and Native American figure in upper right below explanatory note. This image is based upon the 1608 map by Captain John Smith.
  - Virginiae Partis Australis et Floridae Partis Orientalis, Interjacentiumq, Region Nova Descripto, circa 1640 (Folder 2)
    Map of Virginia and Florida published ca. 1640 by Willem Janszoon Blaeu (1571-1638) of Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 21.4 in. x 16.9 in. (54.35 cm x 42.93 cm). Map depicts seventeenth-century Virginia and parts of the southeast Atlantic coast. Large cartouche featuring Native American figures in upper center surrounding titlepiece. Smaller heraldic items in upper right and center of map. Cartouche featuring cherubs surrounds mileage chart in bottom center right.
  - A Map of Virginia and Maryland Sold by Thomas Basset in Fleetstreet and Richard Chiswell in St Paul's Churchyard (1), 1676 (Folder 3)
    By Francis Lamb. Copper plate engraving, color. 20.7 in. x 17 in. (52.57 cm x 43.18 cm). Map depicting seventeenth-century Virginia, Maryland and part of New Jersey. Titlepiece in upper right with cartouche featuring angelic figures. Heraldic symbol with crown in upper left just above scale.
  - Nova Virginiae Tabula, 1671 (Folder 4)
    New Virginia Map by Arnoldis Montanus. Published in Amsterdam in 1671. Copper plate engraving, black and white. 19.3 in. x 16.28 in. (49 cm x 41.35 cm). Map depicts seventeenth-century Virginia. Titlepiece in upper right adorned with images of cherubs. Heraldic image in upper center and Explanatory Note in upper right adorned with figures of Native Americans and animals. Scale in bottom center is also surrounded by cherub figures.
  - A Map of Virginia and Maryland Sold by Thomas Basset in Fleetstreet and Richard Chiswell in St Paul's Churchyard (2), 1676 (Folder 5)
    By Francis Lamb. Copper plate engraving, color. 20.7 in. x 17 in. (52.57 cm x 43.18 cm). Map depicting seventeenth-century Virginia, Maryland, and part of New Jersey. Titlepiece in upper right with cartouche featuring angelic figures. Heraldic symbol with crown in upper left just above scale. This Map has slightly different coloration than Map 3.
  - Nova Belgica et Anglia Nova, circa 1662 (Folder 6)
    New Belgium and New England published ca. 1662 by Joan Blaeu (1597-1663) of Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 24.3 in. x 20.45 in. (61.72 cm x 51.94 cm). Map depicts seventeenth-century New Belgium, New England, and New Netherland. Titlepiece is middle right and decorated with images of Native Americans, heraldic symbol, and crown. Scale is in bottom left and decorated with images of children. Other artwork in the map include vignettes of stockade-fenced settlements, animals, and ships.
  - A New Map of Virginia, Maryland, and the Improved Parts of Pennsylvania and New Jersey, 1719 (Folder 7)
    Map of Virginia, Maryland, Pennsylvania, and New Jersey by John Senex (1678-1740) published 1719 in London. Copper plate engraving, color. 24 in. x 20 in. (60.96 cm x 50.8 cm). Map depicts Virginia, Maryland, Pennsylvania, and New Jersey. Titlepiece in upper left. Scale in lower right.
  - Northeast Coast - Pas Caert van Nieu Nederlandt en du Engelsche Virginies, 1668 (Folder 8)
    Peter Goos. 17x21.
  - Virginia Marylandia et Carolina in America Septentrionali, circa 1740 (Folder 9)
    Homann. 20x23.
  - Virginia and Maryland, circa 1700 (Folder 10)
    Map of Virginia and Maryland by Herman Moll (1654-1732). Published in London ca. 1700. Copper plate Engraving, color. 9.5 in. x 13.85 in. (24.14 cm x 35.18 cm). Map depicts Virginia, Maryland and parts of southern New Jersey. Unadorned titlepiece in upper left.
  - Carte de la Virginie et du Maryland, 1755 (Folder 11)
    Map of Virginia and Maryland by Gilles Robert de Vaugondy (1688-1766) published in 1755. Copper plate engraving, color. 31.75 in x 21.5 in (80.64 cm x 54.61 cm). Map depicting Virginia, Maryland, and parts of Pennsylvania and Delaware. Titlepiece and scale in bottom right has cartouche of flora.
  - The State of Virginia from the Best Authorities, 1794 (Folder 12)
    State of Virginia Map by Samuel Lewis, Philadelphia. Copper plate engraving, black and white. 21.3 in. x 16.9 in. (54.1 cm x 42.9 cm). Map depicting Virginia, the Northwest Territory, and parts of Maryland. Titlepiece with scale in upper left.
  - Map and Chart of parts of Bay of Chesapeake York and James River which are at Present the Seat of War, undated (Folder 13)
    Unidentified. 10x15.
  - A New and Accurate Map of Virginia and Maryland, circa 1752 (Folder 14)
    Map of Virginia and Maryland by Emmanuel Bowen. Copper plate engraving, color. 9.75 in. x 16 in. (24.76 cm x 40.64 cm). Map depicts eighteenth-century Virginia, Maryland, and part of New Jersey. Titlepiece and scale are in bottom right.
  - Nova Terrae-Marie Tabula, 1671 (Folder 15)
    New Map of Maryland by John Ogilby (1600-1676). Copper plate engraving, color. 20.15 in. x 16.21 in. (51.18 cm x 41.17 cm). Map depicts seventeenth-century Maryland and parts of both Virginia, and New Jersey. Ornate Titlepiece is in top center of map. Dedication, adorned with the coat of arms of Lord Baltimore, is in the upper right, and scale in lower left.
  - L'Amerique Septentrionale. Dressee sur les Observations de Mrs. de l'Academie Royale des Sciences & quelques autres, & sur les Memoires les plus recens. Par G. De L' Isle Geographie a Amsterdam chez Pierre Schenk sur le vygendam, al' Atlas de Sanson Avec Privilege 1708 (Folder 16)
    Map of North America by Pierre Schenk (1660-1718) of Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 25 in. x 20.5 in. (63.5 cm x 52.07 cm). Map depicts eighteenth-century North America. European territorial possessions are colored in. Ornately decorated titlepiece featuring mythological sea creatures is in upper right. Advertisement and scale are in upper left.
  - Map of Harbor at Cadiz, 1585 (Folder 17)
    Ortelius. 19x23.
  - Map of the World (unidentified), circa 1680 (Folder 18)
    Copper plate engraving, color. 8 in. x 11 in (20.32 cm x 27.94 cm). Map depicting the world's continents as seen from the vantage point of the North Pole. No identification, though "1680" penciled-in on verso.
  - Americae Sive Novi Orbis, Nova Descripto, circa 1640 (Folder 19)
    America or New World Newly Described by Abraham Ortelius (1528-1598). Copper plate engraving, black and white. 20.25 in x 15.6 in (51.43 cm x 39.62 cm). Map of North and South America. Ornately decorated titlepiece in lower left and sailing ships in center.
  - Insulae Americanae in Oceano Septentrionali cum Terris Adiacentibus, circa late 1500s - early 1600s (Folder 20)
    Map of Caribbean islands and Gulf of Mexico by Willem Janszoon Blaeu (1571-1638) of Amsterdam. Copperplate engraving, color. 23 in. x 19.25 in. (58.42 cm x 48.89 cm). Map depicting Gulf of Mexico and Caribbean Islands and parts of North, South, and Central America. Titlepiece in upper left flanked by cherubs. Ornate dedication in lower left and scale in lower right.
  - America, circa 1710 (Folder 21)
    Map of North and South America by Herman Moll (1654-1732), London. Copper plate engraving, color. 9 in. x 14 in. (22.86 cm x 35.56 cm). Map depicts eighteenth-century North and South America. Titlepiece in top left of map.
  - L'Amerique Septentrionale. Dressee sur les Observations de Mrs. de l'Academie Royale des Sciences & quelques autres, & sur les Memoires les plus recens. Par G. De L' Isle Geographie a Amsterdam chez I. Covens et C. Mortimer. Avec Privilege, circa 1740 (Folder 22)
    Map of North and Central America by Guillame Delisle (1675-1726) of Paris. Copper plate engraving, color. 21 in x 25 in (53.34 cm x 63.5 cm). Map depicting the eastern part of North America and Central America. Ornately decorated titlepiece in upper left featuring mythical sea figures and scale in upper right.
  - The United States of North America with the British Territories and those of Spain, according to the Treaty of 1784. Engraved by Wm Faden, 1796 (Folder 23)
    Map of the United States by William Faden (1750-1836). Published 1796 in London. Copper plate engraving, color. 23 in. x 31 in. (58.42 cm x 78.74 cm). Map depicts the eighteenth-century United States of America and parts of Canada. Titlepiece in bottom right is decorated with images having to do with shipping and trade. Scale is in bottom left.
  - A Draught of Virginia, 1758 (Folder 24)
    Map of Chesapeake Bay Area of Virginia, Mark Tiddeman, London. Copper plate engraving, color. 19 in. x 23.5 in. (48.26 cm x 59.69 cm). Map depicts eighteenth-century Tidewater and Chesapeake Bay area of Virginia. Titlepiece in bottom left. Scale is in bottom center.
  - A New Map of North America from the Latest Discoveries, 1763 (Folder 25)
    Map of North America, J. Spillsbury, London. Copper plate engraving, color. 11 in. x 15 in. (27.94 cm x 38.1 cm). Eighteenth-century map depicting North America. Titlepiece is in bottom right. European territorial claims are delineated by colored outlining.
  - A Map of the British American Plantations Extending from Boston in New England to Georgia; Including all the Back Settlements in the Respective Provinces, as far as the Mississippi, July 1754 (Folder 26)
    Map of American Colonies by Thomas Bowen (1700-1763), London. Copper plate engraving, color. 9 in. x 12 in. (22.86 cm x 30.48 cm). Map depicting the eighteenth-century American colonies. Titlepiece in lower right flanked by images of Native Americans. Scale in middle right.
  - North America. Performed under the Patronage of Louis Duke of Orleans, First Prince of the Blood; by the Sieur D'Anville. Greatly Improved by Mr. Bolton. Engraved by R.W. Seale, MDCCLII, 1752 (Folder 27)
    Map of North America by Simon Bolton and engraved by R.W. Seale. Copper plate engraving, color. 21 in. x 26 in. (53.34 cm x 66.04 cm). Map depicts eighteenth-century British and French North America. Large decorated titlepiece in lower right adorned with images of cherubs, a Native American figure, animals, and plants.
  - Nova Orbis Tabula in Lucem Edita, circa 1670 (Folder 28)
    New Map of the World, by A. F. De wit. Copper plate engraving, color. 19 in. x 23 in. (48.26 cm x 58.42 cm). Seventeenth-century map of the world depicting the eastern and western hemispheres surrounded by images of the seasons, elements, and mythological figures.
  - Mappe Monde qui Represente les deux Hemispheres Savoir celui de l'Orient et celui l'Occident tire'e des Quatre Cartes Generales de feu M. Le Professeur Hafius. Ir effe'e par G.M. Lowitz, et Publie'e par les Heritiers se Homann l'An 1746 (Folder 29)
    World map showing eastern and western hemispheres, G.M. Lowitz. Copper plate engraving, color. 20 in. x 24 in. (49 cm x 41.35 cm). Eighteenth-century map depicting the eastern and western hemispheres of the world. Titlepieces in both upper left (Latin) and upper right (French) adorned with images of flora and fauna. Map has four insets, which depict the Arctic, Antarctic, Horizon of Nuremburg, and the Antipodes of Nuremburg.
  - Asiac Nova Descripto, circa 1640 (Folder 30)
    Blaeu. 17x21.
  - Englalond Anglia Anglosaonvm Heptarchia Terra Armis Animisqve Potens, circa 1607 (Folder 31)
    Map of England and part of Scotland by Guliel Hole (d. 1624). Copper plate engraving, color. 12 in. x 13 in. (30.48 cm x 33.02 cm). Seventeenth-century map of England and Scotland. Titlepiece in upper right adorned with ornate cartouche featuring a crown and colorful embellishments. Large compass rose in lower left.
  - Vectis Insula Anglice: The Isle of Wight, 1648 (Folder 32)
    Map of the Isle of Wight, Joan Bleau (1597-1663) of Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 20 in. x 24 in. (50.8 cm x 60.96 cm). Seventeenth-century map of the Isle of Wight off the southern English coast. Title piece in lower left has cartouche featuring a coat of arms, and animals. Scale, adorned with globe, in lower right.
  - Hantshire, circa 1640 (Folder 33)
    Bleau. 20x24.
  - Dorset, circa 1640 (Folder 34)
    Blaeu. 20x24.
  - England and Wales, 1750 (Folder 35)
    John Rocque. 40x50. London. Two sheets.
  - Wigornmiensis Comitatus Cum Warwicensi, Nec Non Conventriae Libertas (Warwick, England), circa 1646 (Folder 36)
    Map of Warwickshire, England published ca. 1646 by Joan Blaeu (1597-1663) of Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 20 in. x 25 in. (50.8 cm x 63.5 cm). Map depicting seventeenth-century Warwickshire, England. Titlepiece in bottom left decorated with cartouche of fruits and flowers. Coats of arms in top left and bottom right, and scale in top right.
  - Carte Reduite de L'Ocean Occidental, 1766 (Folder 37)
    Bellin. 23x36. Paris.
  - From D'Anville (World), 1788 (Folder 38)
    I. Harrison. 21x32. Two sheet map.
  - Hemisphere Occidental, Dressee en 1720 pour l'usage Particular du Roy sur les Observations Astronomiques et Geographiques Raportees la meme Annee vans l'Histoire et vans les Memoires de l'Acemie Rle. des Sciences Par Guillaume de l'Isle Premier Geographahe de sa Majeste' de la meme Academie (Folder 39)
    Map of the Western Hemisphere published by J. Covens and C. Mortimer in Amsterdam. Copper plate engraving, color. 20 in. x 20 in. (50.8 cm x 50.8 cm). Map depicting eighteenth-century Western Hemisphere (North and South America and Pacific islands). Title in upper part of map. European territorial holdings are outlined in color.
  - St. Christopher's Island, circa 1800 (Folder 40)
    Unidentified. 19x24.
  - Granada, 1778 (Folder 41)
    Unidentified. 21x24. Paris.
  - Isle of St. Vincent, 1778 (Folder 42)
    LaRouge. 21x29. Paris.
  - British Isles, circa 1850 (Folder 43)
    From Pinkerton's Atlas. 24x40. London.
  - The Roads from Chelmsford in Essex to Maldon, Raleigh in Essex [and] Gravesend in Kent, circa 1675 (Folder 44)
    Map of roads between Chelmsford and Dover, England published by John Ogilby (1600-1676). Copper plate engraving, color. 15 in. x 18 in. (38.1 cm x 45.72 cm). Map depicts seventeenth-century road from Chelmsford to Dover, England. Titlepiece is in top center of map with a cartouche of mythological sea creatures and figures.
  - The Road from London to Cambridge, Ely, & Kings Lynn, from Oxford to Cambridge, passing [through] Buckingham & Bedford, circa 1720 (Folder 45)
    Map of road from London to Bury, England by J. Gibson and published circa 1720. Copper plate engraving, color. 7 in. x 12 in. (17.78 cm x 30.48 cm). Map depicts eighteenth-century road from London to Bury, England. Title runs entire length of map at top. Road is divided into ten numbered columns and towns and mileages are labeled.
  - Vrbium Londoni et West Monasterii nec non Suburbii Southwark Accurata Ichnographia, in qua Vie Publicae Omnes et Fingulae, etc. (Map of London), 1736 (Folder 46)
    2-sheet map of southern London by Christophe Homan (1703-30) and published 1736. Copper plate engraving, color. 25 in. x 31 in. (63.5 cm x 78.74 cm). 2-sheet map depicting eighteenth-century south London, England. Titlepiece in lower right with Lion and Unicorn Cartouche. Title of map is in Latin, while place and street names are in English. Other information is in German.
  - Virginia, Maryland, and Delaware, 1825 (Folder 47)
    Map of Virginia, Maryland and Delaware by Henry Schenck Tanner (1786 - 1858), Philadelphia. Engraving, color. 19 in. x 23 in. (48.26 cm x 58.42 cm). Nineteenth-century map depicting Virginia, Maryland, and Delaware. Titlepiece is in top center. Scale and Explanation are in bottom center. Counties within each state are colored, while bordering states are left white.
  - Lot of 8 maps, 1872 (Folder 48 a-h)
    Unidentified. 12x15. Includes: a) Virginia and Maryland, b) Texas, c) Arizona and New Mexica, d) Kentucky and Tennessee, e) Floriday, f) Georgia and Alabama, g) North and South Caroline, h) Baltimore, MD.
  - A Map of the U.S. of A., 1794 (Folder 49)
    Wilkinson. 11x13. London.
  - United States of America, Northern Part, 1810 (Folder 50)
    Cadell and Davies. 23x30. London.
  - Virginia and Maryland with latest improvements, circa 1838 (Folder 51)
    Unidentified. 9x11.
  - Virginia, Delaware, Maryland, and West Virginia, 1864 (Folder 52)
    A. J. Johnson. 18x26. New York.
  - Virginia, Delaware, Maryland, and West Virginia, undated (Folder 53)
    A. J. Johnson. 18x26. Same as item 52, but a different edition.
  - A New Map of Virginia with its Roads Canals and Distances, 1853 (Folder 54)
    Cowperthwait. 14x17. Philadelphia.
  - Georgetown and the City of Washington, 1855 (Folder 55)
    Cotton. 16x18. New York.
  - Georgetown and the City of Washington, circa 1865 (Folder 56)
    Johnson. 14x18. New York. Same as item 55.
  - Virginia, 1855 (Folder 57)
    Colton. 16x18. New York.
  - Map of Virginia and Maryland, circa 1830 (Folder 58)
    Seers & Co. 11x16.
  - A Correct Map of Virginia, circa 1818 (Folder 59)
    Unidentified. 17x21.
  - A New Map of Part of the U.S. of N. America, 1828 (Folder 60)
    Cary. 21x24. London.
  - Geographical Statistical and Historical Map of Virginia, circa 1820 (Folder 61)
    Unidentified. 18x22.
  - Geographical Statistical and Historical Map of the District of Columbia, circa 1820 (Folder 62)
  - Johnson's Map of Vicinity of Richmond and the Peninsular Campaign, 1862 (Folder 63)
    Unidentified. 18x27. New York.
  - Plan of the City of Washington, post 1800 (Folder 64)
  - Tabula Geographica Principatus Anhaltini et Finitionaum Regionum, circa 1680 (Folder 65)
    Begin. 15x17.
  - Lisbona, circa 1740 (Folder 66)
    Seutter. 221x25. Pictorial map with scene of burning of Lisbon.
  - Topographical Map of the District of Columbia with the Fortification around the City (Civil War), undated (Folder 67)
    Unidentified. 16x32.
  - Map of the State of Virginia Reduced from the Nine Sheet Map of the State in Conformity to Law, 1827 (Folder 68)
    Herman Boye. 31x50. Example of the first official map of Virginia backed with cloth in slip case.
  - Campaign Maps (Civil War), 1867 (Folder 69)
    Major J.E. Wayes. 22x25. New York. Maps include 1) Petersburg and Five Forks, 2) Antietam, 3) Spotsylvania Courthouse, and 4) Richmond; folded maps each with a hard cover. In 2 folders.
  - Map of the Battlefield of Fredericksburgh (Civil War), 1866 (Folder 70)
    Blackford. 20x24. Baltimore. Folded map with hard cover.
  - The Tourist's Pocket Map of the State of Virginia, 1835 (Folder 71)
    Young. 13x16. Philadelphia.
  - Map of the States of Louisiana, Mississippi, and Alabama, 1834 (Folder 72)
    Mitchell (publisher). 22x18. Philadelphia. Folding traveler's map in red morocco folder (3x5); map torn in folds, folder chipped and rubbed. In the same folder as item 70.
  - Darien, 1698 (Folder 73)
    By Richard Long. 21x25. Manuscript map on parchment showing the future site of the Scottish Colony near Panama which existed from 1698 to 1699, when it was captured by the Spanish Army. Darien was to be the Scottish Jamestown and was part of the British effort to expand southward into the Caribbean. The few survivors found refuge in Jamaica.
  - Norumbega et Virginia, 1597 (Folder 74)
    Wytfliet. 9x12. Louvon.
  - Angliae Regni...(England), 1573 (Folder 75)
    Ortelius. 17x21. Map from early atlas.
  - Nova Virginia Tabula, circa 1620 (Folder 76)
    Hondius. 19x23. Hondius edition of John Smith map of 1608.
  - Title page from Blaeu Atlas, 1640 (Folder 77)
    12x19. Amsterdam.
  - Engraving of Ceremonies of Virginia and the King of Pegu, circa 1650 (Folder 78)
    Leide. 15x19.
  - Map of N. E. Virginia and vicinity of Washington, 1862 (Folder 79)
    27x29. Washington D.C.
  - Delaware, 1796 (Folder 84)
  - Map of Arlington and Vicinity (street indexed), 1955 (Folder 85)
  - Map of the City of Richmond, Virginia, 1861-1865, 1961 (Folder 86)
  - Mineral Industries and Resources of Virginia, 1959 (Folder 87)
  - Map of Present Richmond, Virginia, 1961 (Folder 88)
  - The New World, Reproduction of map from 1600 (Folder 89)
  - The Oldest Map of the New World, Reproduction of map from 1493-1496 (Folder 90)
  - Alexandria Quadrangle, Virginia - District of Columbia - Maryland, 1951 (Folder 91)
  - Washington and Vicinity, 1917 (Folder 92)
  - County of Arlington Virginia, July 15, 1950 (Folder 93)